
Name                                                     DisplayName                                                                     Description                                         
----                                                     -----------                                                                     -----------                                         
Rsat.ActiveDirectory.DS-LDS.Tools~~~~0.0.1.0             RSAT: Active Directory Domain Services and Lightweight Directory Services Tools Active Directory Domain Services (AD DS) and Acti...
Rsat.BitLocker.Recovery.Tools~~~~0.0.1.0                 RSAT: BitLocker Drive Encryption Administration Utilities                       BitLocker Drive Encryption Administration Utiliti...
Rsat.CertificateServices.Tools~~~~0.0.1.0                RSAT: Active Directory Certificate Services Tools                               Active Directory Certificate Services Tools inclu...
Rsat.DHCP.Tools~~~~0.0.1.0                               RSAT: DHCP Server Tools                                                         DHCP Server Tools include the DHCP MMC snap-in, D...
Rsat.Dns.Tools~~~~0.0.1.0                                RSAT: DNS Server Tools                                                          DNS Server Tools include the DNS Manager snap-in,...
Rsat.FailoverCluster.Management.Tools~~~~0.0.1.0         RSAT: Failover Clustering Tools                                                 Failover Clustering Tools include the Failover Cl...
Rsat.FileServices.Tools~~~~0.0.1.0                       RSAT: File Services Tools                                                       File Services Tools include snap-ins and command-...
Rsat.GroupPolicy.Management.Tools~~~~0.0.1.0             RSAT: Group Policy Management Tools                                             Group Policy Management Tools include Group Polic...
Rsat.IPAM.Client.Tools~~~~0.0.1.0                        RSAT: IP Address Management (IPAM) Client                                       IP Address Management (IPAM) Client is used to co...
Rsat.LLDP.Tools~~~~0.0.1.0                               RSAT: Data Center Bridging LLDP Tools                                           Data Center Bridging LLDP Tools include PowerShel...
Rsat.NetworkController.Tools~~~~0.0.1.0                  RSAT: Network Controller Management Tools                                       Network Controller Management Tools include Power...
Rsat.NetworkLoadBalancing.Tools~~~~0.0.1.0               RSAT: Network Load Balancing Tools                                              Network Load Balancing Tools include the Network ...
Rsat.RemoteAccess.Management.Tools~~~~0.0.1.0            RSAT: Remote Access Management Tools                                            Remote Access Management Tools include graphical ...
Rsat.RemoteDesktop.Services.Tools~~~~0.0.1.0             RSAT: Remote Desktop Services Tools                                             Remote Desktop Services Tools include snap-ins fo...
Rsat.ServerManager.Tools~~~~0.0.1.0                      RSAT: Server Manager                                                            Server Manager includes the Server Manager consol...
Rsat.Shielded.VM.Tools~~~~0.0.1.0                        RSAT: Shielded VM Tools                                                         Shielded VM Tools include the Provisioning Data F...
Rsat.StorageMigrationService.Management.Tools~~~~0.0.1.0 RSAT: Storage Migration Service Management Tools                                Provides management tools for storage migration j...
Rsat.StorageReplica.Tools~~~~0.0.1.0                     RSAT: Storage Replica Module for Windows PowerShell                             Includes PowerShell module to remotely manage the...
Rsat.SystemInsights.Management.Tools~~~~0.0.1.0          RSAT: System Insights Module for Windows PowerShell                             System Insights module for Windows PowerShell pro...
Rsat.VolumeActivation.Tools~~~~0.0.1.0                   RSAT: Volume Activation Tools                                                   Volume activation Tools can be used to manage vol...
Rsat.WSUS.Tools~~~~0.0.1.0                               RSAT: Windows Server Update Services Tools                                      Windows Server Update Services Tools include grap...